http://www.lurssen.com/en/privacy-policy/

icons-lifetime-support_solidicons-lifetime-support_solidicons-lifetime-support_solidicons-lifetime-support_solidicons-lifetime-support_solidicons-lifetime-support_solidicons-lifetime-support_solidicons-lifetime-support_solidHomeNew Build
About
RefitLifetime SupportNews / Media / Events
ContactHomeNew BuildPreviewDesignSketchbookYoung DesignerEngineeringManufactureThe YachtsLifetime SupportAboutPreview11 ReasonsHistoryLocationsSustainabilityRefitLifetime SupportNews / Media / EventsPreviewNews / Social MediaEventsPress ReleasesMedia EchoLürssen Live!ContactLürssen on FacebookLürssen on YoutubeLürssen on InstagramFollow usSupplierCareerImprintPrivacy Policy
en
ru
zh
de
Privacy Policy1. An overview of data protectionGeneralThe following gives a simple overview of what happens to your personal information when you visit our website. Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified. Detailed information on the subject of data protection can be found in our privacy policy found below.Data collection on our websiteWho is responsible for the data collection on this website?The data collected on this website are processed by the website operator. The operator's contact details can be found in the website's required legal notice.How do we collect your data?Some data are collected when you provide it to us. This could, for example, be data you enter on a contact form. Other data are collected automatically by our IT systems when you visit the website. These data are primarily technical data such as the browser and operating system you are using or when you accessed the page. These data are collected automatically as soon as you enter our website.What do we use your data for?Part of the data is collected to ensure the proper functioning of the website. Other data can be used to analyze how visitors use the site.What rights do you have regarding your data?You always have the right to request information about your stored data, its origin, its recipients, and the purpose of its collection at no charge. You also have the right to request that it be corrected, blocked, or deleted. You can contact us at any time using the address given in the legal notice if you have further questions about the issue of privacy and data protection. You may also, of course, file a complaint with the competent regulatory authorities.Analytics and third-party toolsWhen visiting our website, statistical analyses may be made of your surfing behavior. This happens primarily using cookies and analytics. The analysis of your surfing behavior is usually anonymous, i.e. we will not be able to identify you from this data. You can object to this analysis or prevent it by not using certain tools. Detailed information can be found in the following privacy policy. You can object to this analysis. We will inform you below about how to exercise your options in this regard.2. General information and mandatory informationData protectionThe operators of this website take the protection of your personal data very seriously. We treat your personal data as confidential and in accordance with the statutory data protection regulations and this privacy policy. If you use this website, various pieces of personal data will be collected. Personal information is any data with which you could be personally identified. This privacy policy explains what information we collect and what we use it for. It also explains how and for what purpose this happens. Please note that data transmitted via the internet (e.g. via email communication) may be subject to security breaches. Complete protection of your data from third-party access is not possible.Notice concerning the party responsible for this websiteThe party responsible for processing data on this website is: Fr. Lürssen Werft GmbH & Co. KG Telefon: +49 (0) 421 6604 0 E-Mail: yachts@lurssen.com The responsible party is the natural or legal person who alone or jointly with others decides on the purposes and means of processing personal data (names, email addresses, etc.).Revocation of your consent to the processing of your dataMany data processing operations are only possible with your express consent. You may revoke your consent at any time with future effect. An informal email making this request is sufficient. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed.Right to file complaints with regulatory authoritiesIf there has been a breach of data protection legislation, the person affected may file a complaint with the competent regulatory authorities. The competent regulatory authority for matters related to data protection legislation is the data protection officer of the German state in which our company is headquartered. A list of data protection officers and their contact details can be found at the following link: https://www.bfdi.bund.de/DE/Infothek/Anschriften_Links/anschriften_links-node.html.SSL or TLS encryptionThis site uses SSL or TLS encryption for security reasons and for the protection of the transmission of confidential content, such as the inquiries you send to us as the site operator. You can recognize an encrypted connection in your browser's address line when it changes from "http://" to "https://" and the lock icon is displayed in your browser's address bar. If SSL or TLS encryption is activated, the data you transfer to us cannot be read by third parties.Information, blocking, deletionAs permitted by law, you have the right to be provided at any time with information free of charge about any of your personal data that is stored as well as its origin, the recipient and the purpose for which it has been processed. You also have the right to have this data corrected, blocked or deleted. You can contact us at any time using the address given in our legal notice if you have further questions on the topic of personal data.3. Data protection officerStatutory data protection officerWe have appointed a data protection officer for our company. IT-Emotion & Security GmbH & Co.KG Edisonstraße 58 24145 Kiel
Herr Michael Braun
HRB 13834 KI Steuernummer 20/284/58103 Telephone: +49 421 6604 135001 Email: privacy@luerssen.de4. Data collection on our websiteCookiesSome of our web pages use cookies. Cookies do not harm your computer and do not contain any viruses. Cookies help make our website more user-friendly, efficient, and secure. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer and saved by your browser. Most of the cookies we use are so-called "session cookies." They are automatically deleted after your visit. Other cookies remain in your device's memory until you delete them. These cookies make it possible to recognize your browser when you next visit the site. You can configure your browser to inform you about the use of cookies so that you can decide on a case-by-case basis whether to accept or reject a cookie. Alternatively, your browser can be configured to automatically accept cookies under certain conditions or to always reject them, or to automatically delete cookies when closing your browser. Disabling cookies may limit the functionality of this website. Cookies which are necessary to allow electronic communications or to provide certain functions you wish to use (such as the shopping cart) are stored pursuant to Art. 6 paragraph 1, letter f of GDPR. The website operator has a legitimate interest in the storage of cookies to ensure an optimized service provided free of technical errors. If other cookies (such as those used to analyze your surfing behavior) are also stored, they will be treated separately in this privacy policy.Server log filesThe website provider automatically collects and stores information that your browser automatically transmits to us in "server log files". These are: - Browser type and browser version - Operating system used - Referrer URL - Host name of the accessing computer - Time of the server request - IP address These data will not be combined with data from other sources. The basis for data processing is Art. 6 (1) (b) GDPR, which allows the processing of data to fulfill a contract or for measures preliminary to a contract.Contact formShould you send us questions via the contact form, we will collect the data entered on the form, including the contact details you provide, to answer your question and any follow-up questions. We do not share this information without your permission. We will, therefore, process any data you enter onto the contact form only with your consent per Art. 6 (1)(a) GDPR. You may revoke your consent at any time. An informal email making this request is sufficient. The data processed before we receive your request may still be legally processed. We will retain the data you provide on the contact form until you request its deletion, revoke your consent for its storage, or the purpose for its storage no longer pertains (e.g. after fulfilling your request). Any mandatory statutory provisions, especially those regarding mandatory data retention periods, remain unaffected by this provision.Making contactData for sending email invitations If you register on our website for an event or in order to receive notifications about future events, we need both your email address as well as information that allows us to verify that this is your email address and that you agree to receive information relevant to this or future events.No other data will be collected, or, if it is, only on a voluntary basis. We use this data solely for sending the requested information, and we do not pass it on to third parties. This data is processed exclusively on the basis of your consent (Article 6, paragraph 1(a), of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)). You may revoke your consent to the archiving of data, your email address and its use to send you information on events or invitations to future events at any time by sending an email to the address given in the invitation. This does not affect the lawfulness of any data-processing transactions that have taken place to date. The data you have provided us with for the purpose of receiving event information and invitations will be stored by us until you unsubscribe from the mailing list, and it will be deleted from the mailing list if you cancel your subscription. Data stored by us for other purposes remains unaffected. If you unsubscribe from the distribution list, we may store your email address in a blacklist to prevent future mailings. The data from the blacklist will only be used for this purpose and will not be merged with other data. This serves both your interest and our interest in complying with the legal requirements when sending emails (legitimate interest within the meaning of Article 6, paragraph 1(f), of the GDPR). Storage of data in the blacklist is not limited in time. You may object to the storage if your interest takes precedence over our legitimate interest. Advertising (Article 21 of the GDPR) In the event that data is processed based on Article 6, paragraph 1(e) or (f), of the GDPR, you have the right to object at any time to the he processing of your personal data based on grounds arising from your unique situation. This also applies to any profiling based on these provisions. The legal basis on which processing of data is based can be found in this data protection declaration. If you object, we will no longer process your relevant personal data, unless we can demonstrate compelling reasons for processing which are worthy of protection and which take precedence over your interests, rights an freedoms, or the processing serves to assert, exercise or defend legal claims (objection pursuant to Article 21, paragraph 1, of the GDPR). If your personal data is processed for the purpose of direct advertising, you have the right to object at any time to the processing of your relevant personal data for the purpose of such advertising. This also includes profiling to the extent that it is linked to such direct advertising. If you object, your personal data will subsequently no longer be used for direct advertising purposes (objection pursuant to Article 21, paragraph 2, of the GDPR).5. Our social media pagesData processing by social networksWe maintain publicly accessible profiles on social networks. The social networks we use in detail can be found below. Social networks can usually comprehensively analyse your user behaviour when you visit their website or a website with integrated social media content (e.g. with like buttons or advertising banners). Visiting our social media sites triggers numerous processing procedures which are relevant to data protection. In detail If you are logged into your social media account and visit one of our social media pages, the operator of the social media portal can assign this visit to your user account. However, your personal data may also be collected if you are not logged in or do not have an account with the social media portal in question. In this case, this data will be collected, for example, via cookies that are stored on your terminal device or by recording your IP address. With the help of the data collected in this way, the operators of the social media portals can create user profiles in which your preferences and interests are stored. In this way, advertisements related to your interests can be displayed both inside and outside of the social media site concerned. If you have an account with that social network, advertising based on your interests may be displayed on all devices you are or have been logged on to. Please also note that we cannot track all of the processing which is carried out on social media portals. Depending on the provider, the operators of the social media portals may be able to carry out further processing operations. Details can be found in the terms of use and data protection regulations of the social media portals concerned.The legal basisOur social media sites are designed to ensure the widest possible presence on the internet. This is a legitimate interest within the meaning of the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR) art. 6 para. 1 lit. f. The analysis processes initiated by the social networks may rely on a different legal basis, which must be stated by the operators of the social networks (e.g. consent within the meaning of GDPR art. 6 para. 1 lit. a).Person responsible and assertion of rightsWhen you visit one of our social media sites, we are jointly responsible with the operator of the social media platform for the data processing operations triggered by that visit. You can assert your rights (information, correction, deletion, restriction of processing, data transferability and complaint) both against us and against the operator of the respective social media portal. Please note that despite our joint responsibility with the social media portal operators, we do not have full control over their data processing operations. Our options depend to a large extent on the corporate policy of the particular provider.Duration of storageThe data collected directly by us via the social media presence will be deleted from our systems as soon as the purpose for its storage no longer applies, or you request us to delete it, or you revoke your consent to storage, or the reason for storing the data no longer applies. Stored cookies will remain on your device until you delete them. Mandatory legal provisions - in particular retention periods - remain unaffected. We have no influence on the storage period of your data, which is stored by the operators of the social networks for their own purposes. For details, please contact the social network operators directly.Social networks in detailFacebookWe have a profile on Facebook. This service is provided by Facebook Ireland Limited, 4 Grand Canal Square, Dublin 2, Ireland. According to Facebook, the data collected will also be transferred to the USA and other countries. We have signed a joint processing agreement (controller addendum) with Facebook. This agreement sets out the data processing operations that we or Facebook are responsible for when you visit our Facebook page. You can view this agreement at the following link https://www.facebook.com/legal/terms/page_controller_addendum You can adjust your advertising settings independently in your own user account. Click on the following link and log in: https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads. Please refer to Facebook's privacy policy for details: https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/InstagramWe have a profile at Instagram. The provider is Instagram Inc., 1601 Willow Road, Menlo Park, CA, 94025, USA. For details on how we treat your personal information, please refer to Instagram's privacy policy: https://help.instagram.com/519522125107875XINGWe have a profile at XING. The provider is New Work SE, Dammtorstraße 29-32, 20354 Hamburg, Germany. For details on how your personal data is handled, please see XING's privacy policy: https://privacy.xing.com/de/datenschutzerklaerungLinkedInWe have a profile at LinkedIn. The provider is LinkedIn Ireland Unlimited Company, Wilton Plaza, Wilton Place, Dublin 2, Ireland. LinkedIn is certified according to the EU-US-PrivacyShield. LinkedIn uses advertising cookies. If you would like to disable LinkedIn advertising cookies, please use the following link: https://www.linkedin.com/psettings/guest-controls/retargeting-opt-out For details on how we handle your personal data, please see LinkedIn's privacy policy: https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policyYouTubeWe have a profile at YouTube. The provider is Google Ireland Limited, Gordon House, Barrow Street, Dublin 4 Ireland. Google uses advertising cookies. You can adjust your advertising settings independently in your own user account. To do that, click on the following link and log in: https://policies.google.com/privacy#infochoices For details on how we handle your personal data, please see YouTube's privacy policy: https://policies.google.com/privacyAllow Matomo TrackingFeel free to contact us should you have any questionsWe are always glad to hear from youContactyachts@lurssen.comFollow usLürssen on FacebookLürssen on YoutubeLürssen on InstagramClick to visit Contact
